<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>TradeStation/アクティビティバー on 投資で実現！不労所得生活</title><link>https://memoja.net/p/vnrcxmf/</link><description>Recent content in TradeStation/アクティビティバー on 投資で実現！不労所得生活</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>ja-jp</language><atom:link href="https://memoja.net/p/vnrcxmf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>TradeStation/アクティビティバー/Price Distribution（プライス・ディストリビューション）</title><link>https://memoja.net/p/fbpxvp3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://memoja.net/p/fbpxvp3/</guid><description>WA-Price Distribution { Search Tag: WA-Price Distribution } { This study plots the basic ActivityBar, together with a value area zone based on standard deviations around the ActivityBar&amp;#39;s mode price. } inputs: ApproxNumRows( 10 ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;ApproxNumRows&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Aprroximate Number of Rows. Enter the approximate number of rows to use in the study.&amp;#34;], CycleColors( true ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;CycleColors&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Enter true to cycle colors from one cell group to the next; enter false to use only a single color for all cells.</description></item><item><title>TradeStation/アクティビティバー/WA-Volume Distribution（ボリューム・ディストリビューション）</title><link>https://memoja.net/p/c2qkjx3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://memoja.net/p/c2qkjx3/</guid><description>WA-Volume Distribution { Search Tag: WA-Volume Distribution } { This study plots a modified ActivityBar, with each ActivityData bar being processed either once or not at all depending on whether its volume is above or below the specified BlockSize. If BlockSize is set to zero, each ActivityData bar is processed, resulting in the basic ActivityBar plot of the Price Distribution ActivityBar study. } inputs: ApproxNumRows( 10 ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;ApproxNumRows&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Aprroximate Number of Rows.</description></item><item><title>TradeStation/アクティビティバー/WA-Candlestick VolAccum（ローソク足出来高アキュムレーション）</title><link>https://memoja.net/p/p3omdnr/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://memoja.net/p/p3omdnr/</guid><description>WA-Candlestick VolAccum { Search Tag: WA-Candlestick VolAccum } { This study plots an ActivityBar that simulates a candlestick, with the width of the candlestick body varying in proportion to the volume of the ActivityBar. } using elsystem.drawing; using elsystem.drawingobjects; inputs: BlockSize( 100 ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;BlockSize&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Enter the amount of volume that will cause the width of the candlestick to be increased.&amp;#34;], MaxNumCells( 100 ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;MaxNumCells&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Maximum Number of Cells.</description></item><item><title>TradeStation/アクティビティバー/WA-Up vs Down Strength（上昇・下落ストレングス）</title><link>https://memoja.net/p/4wnw4rp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://memoja.net/p/4wnw4rp/</guid><description>WA-Up vs Down Strength { Search Tag: WA-Up vs Down Strength } { This study is somewhat similar to the Volume Strength ActivityBar study. As in that study, it plots an ActivityBar in which each ActivityData bar is processed 0 or more times depending on its volume and the specified BlockSize divisor. If BlockSize is set to zero, each ActivityData bar is processed exactly once. The difference is that each time an ActivityData bar is processed, at most one cell is added instead of a range of cells: - if the ActivityData bar was an up bar, one cell is added to the right - if the ActivityData bar was a down bar, one cell is added to the left - if the ActivityData bar was unchanged, no cells are added } inputs: ApproxNumRows( 10 ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;ApproxNumRows&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Aprroximate Number of Rows.</description></item><item><title>TradeStation/アクティビティバー/WA-Volume Strength（出来高強度）</title><link>https://memoja.net/p/8eemvwj/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://memoja.net/p/8eemvwj/</guid><description>WA-Volume Strength { Search Tag: WA-Volume Strength } { This study plots a modified ActivityBar, with each ActivityData bar being processed 0 or more times depending on its volume and the specified BlockSize divisor. If BlockSize is set to zero, each ActivityData bar is processed exactly once, resulting in the basic ActivityBar plot of the Price Distribution ActivityBar study. } inputs: ApproxNumRows( 10 ) [DisplayName = &amp;#34;ApproxNumRows&amp;#34;, ToolTip = &amp;#34;Approximate Number of Rows.</description></item></channel></rss>